Blackboard Course Management System Records UA229
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Blackboard Course Management System Records
2000 -- 2011
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Arts and Sciences
Tufts University
School of Engineering
Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
School of Dental Medicine
School of Medicine
Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine
Gordon Institute
Tisch College
Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
Osher Lifelong Learning Institute
Boston School of Occupational Therapy
UA229
4.15 Linear Feet 4 boxes
1 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into five series: Academic course listings; Technology workshops; Tufts libraries; Tufts organizations; and Unprocessed accessions.
Custodial History
Digital Collections and Archives was approached by Informational Technology Services in April, 2013 regarding the upcoming retirement of the Blackboard Course Management System. DCA staff were granted a generic login and the staff explored options for retrieving course documents, such as syllabi and descriptions, from the system. Due to the proprietary nature of Blackboard, it proved prohibitively difficult to extract digital content from the system in a usable form. The staff determined that the most efficient method for extracting data would be to print the relevant documents out the system. Following the hierarchical tree of the system, DCA student workers reviewed each course and selected the syllabi, course descriptions, and assignment description documents, were available, for printing. All courses were then double-checked by a member of the DCA staff. When accessing pages and documents for printing, the Blackboard system would often impose the access date of the printing date on the document. Any dates on the documents from spring 2013 should be viewed as printing dates only.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment documents harvested from the Blackboard Course Management System at the time of its retirement in 2013.
Biographical / Historical
Since 1955, Tufts University has continued to expand its horizons. In 1964, in one of Wessell's final acts as president, Tufts opened the Experimental College. The Ex-College, which allows students to take classes not normally found in the curriculum, has remained one of Tufts' most popular programs.
In 1977, Tufts established a five-year joint degree program with the New England Conservatory of Music. Soon after, in 1979, a similar program began with the School of the Museum of Fine Arts. Also in 1979, the Tufts Center for European Studies in Talloires, France, was established in an 11th Century priory. The Tufts European Center began operation soon after.
In late 1979, Tufts made another important addition. In October, the Tufts University School of Veterinary Medicine opened at its original Boston campus. In 1980, the Grafton campus, built on the site of a state mental hospital, officially opened its doors.
The last two major additions to Tufts University took place in 1980 and 1981. In 1980, the Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, established with a large grant from the Sackler family, opened its doors on the Boston campus of the Tufts School of Medicine. In 1981, at the Medford Campus, Tufts celebrated the opening of the School of Nutrition Science and Policy. The school was the first of its kind in the nation.
Since Tufts College was officially established in 1852, it has continued to grow and expand in new directions. From its beginnings as a small liberal arts college through its expansion into a full-scale university, Tufts has maintained a strong academic tradition and a community feel.
Conditions Governing Access
University records are closed for 20 years from the date of their creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Information Systems; Curriculum and Instruction -- Teaching Material
- Academic course listings, 2000 -- 2011; UA229.001; 2.4 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions from various schools and departments across all Tufts campuses and disciplines.
  Arrangement
  The series is arranged into twelve sub-series: I. Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; II. School of Engineering; III. School of Liberal Arts; IV. Boston School of Occupational Therapy; V: Master of Public Health Degree Program; VI; Osher Lifelong Learning Institute; VII: School of Dental Medicine; VIII: School of Medicine; IX: School of Nutrition Science and Policy; X: School of Veterinary Medicine; XI: The Gordon Institute; XII: Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service.
  Conditions Governing Access
  20 years from date of creation. Open for research.
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 2000 -- 2011; UA229.001.001; 1.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions for courses offered within the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System.
    This sub-series is arranged into three groups: I: Diplomacy, History and Politics; II: Economics and International Business; and III: International Law and Organizations. Within each group, materials are arranged alphabetically by the name of the instructor teaching the course.
    - Diplomacy, History and Politics, 2000 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001
      Open for research.
      - Blackboard Academic Suite top navigation, 2000 -- 2010; UA229.001.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
        20 years from date of creation.
      - Diplomacy, History, and Politics A-B, 2003 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
      - Diplomacy, History, and Politics C-G, 2007 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
      - Diplomacy, History, and Politics H-I, 2005 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
        No I's
      - Diplomacy, History, and Politics J-L, 2008 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
      - Diplomacy, History, and Politics M-Q, 2007 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
        No Q's
      - Diplomacy, History, and Politics R-T, 2007 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
        No T's
      - Diplomacy, History, and Politics U-Z, 2008 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
        No Z's
    - Economics and International Business, 2006 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.002
      - Economics and International Business A-J, 2008 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
      - Economics and International Business K-M, 2006 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
      - Economics and International Business N-Z, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - International Law and Organizations, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.003
      - International Law and Organizations A-Z, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.001.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
        No X,Y, or Z
  - School of Engineering, 2002 -- 2011; UA229.001.002; 1.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions for courses offered within the School of Engineering as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System.
    This sub-series is arranged by department. Within each department, materials are arranged alphabetically by the name of the instructor teaching the course.
    - Bioengineering-Biomedical Engineering, 2010 -- 2011; UA229.001.002.001.00013 (Box 1)
    - Chemical/Biological Engineering, 2011; UA229.001.002.001.00014 (Box 1)
    - Civil Engineering, 2002 -- 2011; UA229.001.002.001.00015 (Box 1)
    - Computer Science, 2011; UA229.001.002.001.00016 (Box 1)
      No course materials
    - Electrical Engineering, 2008 -- 2009; UA229.001.002.001.00017 (Box 1)
    - Engineering Psychology, 2008; UA229.001.002.001.00018 (Box 1)
    - Engineering Science, 2006 -- 2010; UA229.001.002.001.00019 (Box 1)
    - Engineering-Introductory-Labs, 2010; UA229.001.002.001.00020 (Box 1)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 2006 -- 2009; UA229.001.002.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - School of Liberal Arts, 2005 -- 2011; UA229.001.003; 2.4 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions for courses offered within the School of Liberal Arts as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System.
    - Africa and the New World, 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00022 (Box 1)
      No course materials.
    - All College Listing, 2007; UA229.001.003.001.00023 (Box 1)
    - American Studies, 2008 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00024 (Box 1)
    - Anthropology, 2007 -- 2008; UA229.001.003.001.00025 (Box 1)
    - Arabic, 2008 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00026 (Box 1)
    - Archeology, 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00027 (Box 1)
    - Art History, 2009 -- 2010; UA229.001.003.001.00028 (Box 1)
    - Astronomy, 2009; UA229.001.003.001.00029 (Box 1)
    - Biology, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00030 (Box 1)
    - Center for Interdisciplinary Studies, 2010; UA229.001.003.001.00031 (Box 1)
      No course documents.
    - Chemistry, 2009; UA229.001.003.001.00032 (Box 1)
    - Child Development, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00033 (Box 1)
    - Chinese, 2010; UA229.001.003.001.00034 (Box 1)
    - Classics, 2009 -- 2010; UA229.001.003.001.00035 (Box 1)
    - College of Special Studies, 2010; UA229.001.003.001.00036 (Box 1)
    - Community Health, 2010; UA229.001.003.001.00037 (Box 1)
    - Dance, 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00038 (Box 1)
    - Drama, 2010; UA229.001.003.001.00039 (Box 1)
    - Economics, 2007 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00040 (Box 1)
    - Education, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00041 (Box 1)
      Fulcrum Institute also represented.
    - English, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00042 (Box 1)
    - Entrepreneurial Leadership, 2010; UA229.001.003.001.00043 (Box 1)
    - Environmental Studies, 2010; UA229.001.003.001.00044 (Box 1)
    - Experimental College, 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00045 (Box 1)
    - French, 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00046 (Box 1)
    - Geology, 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00047 (Box 1)
    - German, 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00048 (Box 1)
    - Greek, 2007 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.001.00049 (Box 1)
    - Hebrew, 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00001 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - History, 2005 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00002 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - International Letters Visual Studies, 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00003 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - International Relations, 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00004 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Italian, 2010 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00005 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Japanese, 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00006 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Judaic Studies, 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00007 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Latin, 2008 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00008 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Mathematics, 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00009 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Modern Languages, 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00010 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Music, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00011 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Occupational Therapy, 2010 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00012 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Peace and Justice Studies, 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00013 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Philosophy, 2008 -- 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00014 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Physical Education, 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00015 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Physics, 2010 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00016 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Political Science, 2006 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00017 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Portuguese, 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00018 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Psychology, 2006 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00019 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Religion, 2009; UA229.001.003.002.00020 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Russian, 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00021 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Sociology, 2006 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00022 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Spanish, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00023 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Studio Arts FAM, 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00024 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Swahili, 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00025 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Urban and Environmental Policy, 2010 -- 2011; UA229.001.003.002.00026 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - Women's Studies, 2010; UA229.001.003.002.00027 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 2010; UA229.001.004; 1.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions for courses offered within the Boston School of Occupational Therapy as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System.
    This sub-series is arranged by as found in the Blackboard hierarchy.
    - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 2010; UA229.001.004.002.00028 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
      See also the School of Liberal Arts Department of Occupational Therapy.
  - Master of Public Health Degree Program, 2005 -- 2011; UA229.001.005; 1.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions for courses offered within the Master of Public Health Degree Program as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System.
    This sub-series is arranged alphabetically by instructor's last name.
    - Master of Public Health Degree Program, 2005 -- 2011; UA229.001.005.002.00029 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Osher Lifelong Learning Institute, 2010; UA229.001.006; 1.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains materials for courses offered by the Osher Lifelong Learning Institute as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System.
    - Osher Lifelong Learning Institute, 2010; UA229.001.006.002.00030 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - School of Dental Medicine, 2010; UA229.001.007; 1 Volumes
    This sub-series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions for courses offered by the School of Dental Medicine as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System.
    - School of Dental Medicine, 2010; UA229.001.007.002.00031 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - School of Medicine, 2010; UA229.001.008; 1.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions for courses offered by the School of Medicine as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System. This does not include materials managed in the TUSK system.
    This sub-series is arranged according to the hierarchy found in Blackboard.
    - School of Medicine, 2010; UA229.001.008.002.00032 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
      No course materials. School of Medicine syllabi available in UA146.
  - School of Nutrition Science and Policy, 2005 -- 2011; UA229.001.009; 1.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions for courses offered by the School of Nutrition Science and Policy as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System.
    - School of Nutrition Science and Policy, A-L, 2006 -- 2011; UA229.001.009.002.00033 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    - School of Nutrition Science and Policy, M-Z, 2005 -- 2011; UA229.001.009.002.00034 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - School of Veterinary Medicine, 2010; UA229.001.010; 1.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions for courses offered by the School of Veterinary Medicine as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System.
    - School of Veterinary Medicine, 2010; UA229.001.012.002.00035 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - The Gordon Institute, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.001.011; 1.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions for courses offered by The Gordon Institute as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System.
    This sub-series is arranged according to the hierarchy presented in Blackboard.
    - The Gordon Institute, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.001.011.002.00036 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service, 2007 -- 2008; UA229.001.012; 1.2 Linear Feet
    This sub-series contains course descriptions, syllabi, and assignment descriptions for courses offered by the Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service as managed in the Blackboard Course Management System.
    - Tisch College, 2007 -- 2008; UA229.001.012.002.00037 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
- Technology workshops, 2003 -- 2007; UA229.002; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains information on various workshops and trainings offered by various technology groups on the Tufts campuses.
  The series is arranged according to the hierarchy presented in the Blackboard Course Management System.
  - Technology workshops, 2003 -- 2007; UA229.002.002.00038 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
- Tufts libraries, 2007; UA229.003; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains information on various workshops and trainings offered by various Tufts libraries.
  - Libraries, 2007; UA229.003.002.00039 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
- Tufts organizations, 2002 -- 2011; UA229.004; 2.95 Linear Feet
  This series contains documentation of various Tufts organizations that utilized Blackboard for their document management.
  - ALO/KENET Project, 2004; UA229.004.002.00040 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Africa and the New World Interdisciplinary Minor, 2004 -- 2006; UA229.004.002.00041 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers 1 of 4, 2005 -- 2008; UA229.004.002.00042 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers 2 of 4, 2003 -- 2006; UA229.004.002.00043 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers 4 of 4 - Photos, 2004 -- 2008; UA229.004.002.00045 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Biomedical Engineering; BFIT; and Archaeology Program, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.002.00046 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Curriculum Committee, 2010 -- 2011; UA229.004.002.00047 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Classics, 2005; UA229.004.002.00048 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Child Development Faculty 1 of 4, 2003 -- 2011; UA229.004.002.00049 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Child Development Faculty 2 of 4, 2003 -- 2011; UA229.004.002.00050 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Child Development Faculty 3 of 4, 2003 -- 2011; UA229.004.002.00051 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Child Development Faculty 4 of 4, 2003 -- 2011; UA229.004.002.00052 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Center for Engineering and Education Outreach, 2005; UA229.004.002.00053 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Chemical and Biological Engineering Department Information, 2004 -- 2010; UA229.004.002.00054 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Civil Military Study Group, 2009 -- 2010; UA229.004.002.00055 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Camps research, 2009 -- 2010; UA229.004.002.00056 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Curso CRUB: Ensenanza y aprendizaje de algebra temprana, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.002.00057 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Drama Department Furniture Stock, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.002.00058 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Disabilities Services Office - Interpreters, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.002.00059 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    No records in directory.
  - Edith Balbach Research Team, 2002 -- 2003; UA229.004.002.00060 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
    Bulk of records from this directory were already represented in the Tufts Digital Library and were not reprinted.
  - Eco-Ambassadors, 2008; UA229.004.002.00061 (Box UA229 Shared 1)
  - Eliot-Pearson Curriculum Committee, 2002; UA229.004.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Eliot-Pearson Graduate Programs Committee, 2002 -- 2010; UA229.004.003.00002 (Box 3)
    No records present in Blackboard.
  - ERGO: Biology Department Reading Group, 2010; UA229.004.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Engineers Without Borders 1 of 7, 2007 -- 2009; UA229.004.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Engineers Without Borders 2 of 7, 2005 -- 2009; UA229.004.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Engineers Without Borders 3 of 7, 2005 -- 2007; UA229.004.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Engineers Without Borders 4 of 7, 2007 -- 2011; UA229.004.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Engineers Without Borders 5 of 7, 2007 -- 2011; UA229.004.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Engineers Without Borders 6 of 7, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.004.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Engineers Without Borders 7 of 7, 2006 -- 2011; UA229.004.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Ex College Alumni Council, 2004 -- 2005; UA229.004.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Friedman Student Council, 2005 -- 2007; UA229.004.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - GA Evaluation, 2005; UA229.004.003.00013 (Box 3)
    Research materials of Drusilla Brown. After consultation with Dr. Brown, only two overarching planning documents were pulled down from Blackboard.
  - Graduate Student Council, 2004 -- 2005; UA229.004.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Humanitarianism, Health and Human Security (HHH) Concentration, 2005; UA229.004.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Jumpstart 1 of 3, 2008 -- 2010; UA229.004.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Jumpstart 2 of 3, 2008 -- 2010; UA229.004.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Jumpstart 3 of 3, 2008 -- 2010; UA229.004.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - K-L, 2010; UA229.004.003.00019 (Box 3)
    No materials present in these folders.
  - Maison Francaise, 2011; UA229.004.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Civil Engineering Practice, 2007; UA229.004.003.00021 (Box 3)
    Long term bridge design.
  - Mindfulness and Meditation for Stress Reduction, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Math, Science, Technology and Engineering Education Program, 2006; UA229.004.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - MTC Grant 1 of 3, 2005; UA229.004.003.00024 (Box 3)
    Some reports in this folder had templates imbedded in their cover pages that printed with the date of printing, rather than the date of creation.
  - MTC Grant 2 of 3, 2005; UA229.004.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - MTC Grant 3 of 3, 2005; UA229.004.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Near Highway Air Pollution Project, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.003.00027 (Box 3)
    Directory was empty.
  - Nutrition School - Student Services/Career Services Center, 2007; UA229.004.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Neubauer Undergraduate Scholars Program, 2005; UA229.004.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Training for Improved Practice: Public Health and Nutrition in Emergencies 1 of 11, 2002 -- 2004; UA229.004.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Training for Improved Practice: Public Health and Nutrition in Emergencies 2 of 11, 2002 -- 2004; UA229.004.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Training for Improved Practice: Public Health and Nutrition in Emergencies 3 of 11, 2002 -- 2004; UA229.004.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Training for Improved Practice: Public Health and Nutrition in Emergencies 4 of 11, 2002 -- 2004; UA229.004.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Training for Improved Practice: Public Health and Nutrition in Emergencies 5 of 11, 2002 -- 2004; UA229.004.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Training for Improved Practice: Public Health and Nutrition in Emergencies 6 of 11, 2002 -- 2004; UA229.004.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Training for Improved Practice: Public Health and Nutrition in Emergencies 7 of 11, 2002 -- 2004; UA229.004.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Training for Improved Practice: Public Health and Nutrition in Emergencies 8 of 11, 2002 -- 2004; UA229.004.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Training for Improved Practice: Public Health and Nutrition in Emergencies 9 of 11, 2002 -- 2004; UA229.004.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Training for Improved Practice: Public Health and Nutrition in Emergencies 10 of 11, 2002 -- 2004; UA229.004.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Training for Improved Practice: Public Health and Nutrition in Emergencies 11 of 11, 2002 -- 2004; UA229.004.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Pro-Social Anti-Social Research Project, 2005; UA229.004.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Design and Production, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.004.00008 (Box 4)
    Sofas and chaises.
  - Rice Media Center, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.004.00009 (Box 4)
    No materials in this directory.
  - Radiation Safety Training, 2007; UA229.004.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - GIFT - Graduate Institute for College Teaching, 2009 -- 2011; UA229.004.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - SOTA - Student Occupational Therapy Assocation, 2008 -- 2011; UA229.004.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Society of Women Engineers, 2005; UA229.004.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - TUSC Lab, 2007; UA229.004.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - TCUJ, 2005 -- 2009; UA229.004.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Tufts Diversity Network, 2005 -- 2010; UA229.004.004.00016 (Box 4)
    This directory was empty.